http://www.lotrolife.com/privacy_policy/

Home | Comic |
About Us | Contact Us | Privacy PolicyForum | Follow Us on Twitter | RSS Feeds
Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy policy
At LotroLife.com we recognize that privacy is important. This
policy describes the ways we collect and use your personal information.
This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered
by LotroLife.com. To make this notice easy to find, we make it
available at the bottom of all of our pages.
How we collect information about you
The only information we collect are related to site contributors. If
you write a comment or if you register as a site contributor, we
collect the following types of information from you:
- Email address you can access
- IP address
Any other information collected would be provided entirely at your choice.
How we use cookies
When you access our website, we, or companies we hire to track how our
website is used, may place small data files called âcookiesâ on your
computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to
improve the quality of our service.
How we use the personal information we collect:
We do not share any of this information with outside parties.
How you can access or change your personal information
You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing your profile.
Search for:
Recent Posts
New Region The Great River Comming to Lotro in Spring 2012
Lotro Expansion Riders of Rohan Comming in Fall 2012
New Lotro Update 5 Screenshots
Lotro Update 5: The Prince of Rohan will launch on December 12
Lotro Mithril Edition with 500 Turbine Points Bonus
Recent CommentsLotRO : le « housing ». on Lotro Housing Trophy Taxidermist Barter ItemEpisode 25: Will You Be Our Valentine? | Casual Stroll to Mordor on Lotro Leveling GuideSpirit on Fishing Guide Hobby Lotrojared on Book4Brennan on Lotro Rideable Horse MountLatest Walkthrough Guides
· Free Turbine Points
· Reputation System
· Leveling guide
· Turbine Points  Bree Land
· Horse Mounts
· Book 1
· Book 2
· Book 3
· Aion: Final Fantasy 15 Rusty Bit, Sturdy Helixhorn, Professor’s Protege, Scraps of Mystery and more
· SW:TOR: Rishi Datacrons
· Aion: Aion INVASION launches today
· Aion: Aion Content Update Coming November 5
· DCUO: Green Arrow New Legends Character
· DCUO: War of The Light Part II to be released by the end of 2014
· DCUO: Booster Bundle promotion returns with new price and auras
